<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Pandora Spin</string>
    <string name="about_pandora">Pandora Spin is a mobile application that allows users to earn rewards by spinning a virtual wheel containing different products. \n \n The app offers users the opportunity to collect 10 spins per day, \n and after completing the spins, \n the user will have to wait for 24 hours to repeat the process. \n \n Terms of Use: \n \n Eligibility: \n Pandora Spin is available to all individuals who are 18 years and above. \n User Accounts: \n To use the app, users must create an account and provide accurate and complete information. \n The user is responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of their account and password and for any activities that occur under their account. \n Spinning the Wheel: \n Users can spin the wheel up to 10 times per day. The results of the spins are random, and the user will earn a reward based on the product they land on. \n Rewards: \n Rewards are credited to the user\'s account immediately after a successful spin. Users can redeem their rewards for cash. \n The value of the rewards is subject to change without prior notice. \n Prohibited Activities: \n Users are prohibited from using any automated system or software to access the app, modifying or attempting to modify any part of the app, engaging in any activity that interferes with the normal operation of the app, or engaging in any fraudulent activity. \n Termination: \n Pandora Spin reserves the right to terminate any user account without notice if the user violates any of the terms of use. \n \n Disclaimer of Warranties: \n \n Pandora Spin makes no warranties or representations about the accuracy, completeness, or reliability of the app or the content therein. \n The app is provided on an basis without warranty of any kind. \n Limitation of Liability: Pandora Spin shall not be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, special, or consequential damages arising from the use of the app. \n Changes to the Terms of Use: Pandora Spin reserves the right to modify the terms of use at any time without notice. \n \n By using Pandora Spin, the user agrees to these terms of use.</string>
</resources>